<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Weather</string>

    <string name="warning_detail">Warning Details</string>
    <string name="warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="hour_before">Refreshed %s hours ago</string>
    <string name="minutes_before">Refreshed %s minutes ago</string>

    <string name="setting_temperature">Temperature Unit</string>
    <string name="setting_update">Automatic Updates</string>

    <string name="setting_no_connect">Not Connected</string>
    <string name="city_manage">Manage cities</string>
    <string name="city_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="policy">Privacy policy</string>

    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="token_invalid">Token invalid</string>
    <string name="inner_error">Server internal error</string>
    <string name="lack_permission">Insufficient permissions, request failed</string>
    <string name="over_time">The server is overwhelmed</string>
    <string name="param_error">Request parameter exception</string>
    <string name="no_info">No corresponding information was found</string>
    <string name="lat_long_error">Longitude and latitude error</string>
    <string name="none">off</string>
    <string name="hour">h</string>
    <string name="metre">m</string>
    <string name="kilometer">KM</string>
    <string name="level">&#160;</string>
    <string name="level_unit">&#160;MPH</string>
    <string name="wind_direction">Wind Direction and Force</string>
    <string name="air_quality">Air Quality</string>
    <string name="humidity">Humidity</string>
    <string name="visibility">Visibility</string>
    <string name="uv_index">UV Index</string>
    <string name="sun_up">&#160;Sunrise</string>
    <string name="sun_down">&#160;Sunset</string>
    <string name="current_time">Current</string>
    <string name="city_exist_tips">The selected city already exists</string>
    <string name="not_net">Please connect to the network</string>
    <string name="add_city">Add City</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="search_tips">Search global cities</string>
    <string name="add_current_position">Add weather for the current location</string>
    <string name="current_position">Current Location</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="locate_added">The current city has been added</string>
    <string name="big_clock_12_hours_format" translatable="false">hh:mm</string>
    <string name="big_clock_24_hours_format" translatable="false">kk:mm</string>
    <!--kk:mm-->
    <string name="date_format">EE, MMMM dd</string>
    <string name="yesterday">Yesterday</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <!--<string name="week_date_format">EEEE MM dd</string>-->
    <string name="week_date_format">EEEE</string>
    <string name="week_date_format_simple">&#160;MM dd</string>
    <string name="loading_tips">During the search, please turn on the GPS and keep the signal clear</string>
    <string name="warn_source">Warning information source:</string>
    <string name="gps_open_tips">Please turn on the GPS service</string>

    <string name="header_pulldown">Continue to pull down to refresh</string>
    <!--<string name="header_release">Release refresh now</string>-->
    <string name="header_refreshing">Refreshing...</string>
    <string name="header_finish">Refresh Completed</string>

    <string name="permission_title">Weather application</string>
    <string name="widget_no_data">No City</string>
    <string name="widget_no_net">No Net</string>
    <string name="permanent_city">Permanent City</string>
    <string name="per_add_city">Add city</string>
    <string name="service_run_notice">The weather service is running</string>
    <string name="message_permission_always_failed">Please give us permission in the settings:\n\n%1$s</string>
    <string name="permission_content">
        \t\t\tThe Weather application provides weather forecasting services. To perform these functions, the application
        requires networking and location information while in use.\n
        \t\t\tThe weather application uses the system network location or Baidu locationing to display your current
        latitude and longitude information based on your location. The application needs to collect and use the relevant
        information: IMEI,etc.\n
        \t\t\tWeather forecasting service in Weather application uses data services provided by third parties, and
        requires the use of your location information.\n
        \t\t\tAbove functions will only be used when you have explicitly authorized it.\n
        \t\t\tIf you do not agree to our collection of the above information, or do not agree to invoke relevant
        permissions/features on your phone, weather services will not work properly. You can click "Exit" to turn off
        data collection and permissions for weather application. Click to view our privacy policy.
    </string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">Thank you for using Water OS. In order to let you experience better Water OS
        services, please read this usage statement carefully first.\n
        Shenzhen Royole Technology Co., Ltd. and its affiliated companies (hereinafter referred to as "Royole", we) are
        committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Therefore, we have developed a privacy policy that covers
        how we collect, use, disclose, transmit and store your personal information when you use our website, mobile
        applications or services. You can use our services in many different ways, such as login to Royole website to
        purchase Royole products, use Royole products, services and so on. Before using our products or services and
        submitting personal information, please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our approach to
        customer privacy.\n
        Our privacy policy includes the following aspects:\n
        Information we collect.\n
        How do we collect and use information.\n
        How do you selectively provide information and how do you access and update it.\n
        Information Sharing and Information Security.\n
        Collection and use of children\'s personal information.\n
        The scope of application and revision of this Privacy Policy.\n\n

        <font color="#000000">
            <b>Ⅰ. The information we collect</b>
        </font>
        \n
        1. Royole collects information for more efficient operation and provides you with the best product experience.
        The information we collect includes:\n
        (1) Personal information (personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact
        someone);\n
        (2) Non-personal information (i.e. data that is not directly associated with any particular individual). If we
        merge non-personal information with personal information, such information will be considered personal
        information during the period of merging.\n
        2. When you use FlexPai, your phone number and some unique identifiers in your FlexPai will be sent to Royole in
        order to provide you with more sincere , convenient and professional services. In the process of registration,
        it is necessary to access the network, use and read short messages and contact information. At any time, your
        information is processed in accordance with Royole\'s privacy policy, which can be browsed in "Settings > About
        Mobile Phone > Legal Information".\n
        3. The following system services need networking, positioning and other operations, including:\n
        (1) System data updating service, system updating, telephone service, InCallUI, lock screen, desktop, number
        ownership, user feedback and so on need to be networked in the use process.\n
        (2) Weather needs to use your location information in the use process.\n
        (3) The flashlight needs to use camera flash.\n
        (4) Intelligent identification of unfamiliar numbers provides unfamiliar number identification services,
        including identification of suspected fraud, advertising harassment and other telephone numbers. The use of this
        service requires networking and positioning authority.\n
        (5) Online Risk Recognition Web Site provides the function of identifying malicious Web sites in short messages,
        which requires network privileges.\n
        (6) Intelligent Services provide travel management, road condition reminder, event reminder, health reminder and
        other services. Using this service requires networking, acquiring current location information, reading
        information, calendar, calling WLAN, Bluetooth switch, reading/modifying external memory, and the rights of
        contacts.\n\n

        <font color="#000000">
            <b>Ⅱ. How do we collect and use information.</b>
        </font>
        \n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>1. Collection and use of personal information</b>
        </font>
        \n
        When you interact with us, you may be asked to provide some personal information you need to agree to use our
        basic product services. This personal information may be combined with other information and used to improve our
        products or services.
        Below are some examples of the types of personal information that Royole may collect and how we use it.\n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>1.1 Person Information Collection</b>
        </font>
        \n
        When you create Royole account, download and update Royole software, register in Royole online retail store,
        participate in online survey or participate in other interaction with Royole, we will ask you to provide
        personal information, including but not limited to your name, telephone number, e-mail address, mailing address,
        etc.\n
        When you purchase Royole products and services, we collect personal information, including but not limited to:
        delivery details, bank accounts, credit card details, billing address, credit verification and other financial
        information, contact and communication records.\n
        When you use Royole products to share your content with family and friends, send messages and products, or
        invite others to the Royole Forum, Royole will collect personal information related to the above people, such as
        name, mailing address, e-mail address and telephone number.\n
        When you first use and activate Royole mobile device, your mobile user identification information, unique
        identification code of mobile device and the approximate location information of your device will be sent to
        Royole. In the sending process, the operator only collects traffic or basic information fees. The above
        information collection may also be applicable to your updating system or software, restoring factory settings,
        etc.\n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>1.2 Personal Information Use</b>
        </font>
        \n
        Royole will strictly abide by this Privacy Policy and its updates to use your personal information. Your
        personal information will be used only for purposes that have been identified and agreed upon by you at the time
        of collection. If there are any other uses besides this, we will ask for your consent in advance.\n
        Our personal information collected will be used to provide you with Royole\'s products and services, to process
        your orders or to fulfill your contract with Royole to ensure the functionality and safety of our products and
        services, to verify your identity, and to prevent and prosecute fraud or other misuse.\n
        The personal information we collect will be used for the development of our products and services, although in
        general, we only use comprehensive and statistical information for this purpose.\n
        The personal information we collect will be used to communicate with you. For example, we will notify you at the
        first time of update and release of Royole products or services.\n
        The personal information we collect will be used for personalized design of products and provide you with more
        personal services, such as recommendation in our services, display of content and advertisements specially
        created for you, or research.\n
        If you participate in lottery, competition or similar promotional activities organized by Royole, we will use
        your personal information to manage such activities.\n
        Your mobile user identification information, unique mobile device identification number and geographic location
        information can be used to activate your warranty service and specific software licenses, and you may be invited
        to participate in the survey. We will also use this information to improve our products and analyze the
        efficiency of our business operations. But we will not use this information to track your location.\n\n

        <font color="#000000">
            <b>2. Collection and use of non-personal information</b>
        </font>
        \n
        At the same time, in order to operate and improve Royole\'s technology and services, Royole will collect and use
        your non-personal information by itself, which will help Royole to provide you with a better user experience and
        improve Royole\'s service quality.
        Below are some examples of non-personal information that we may collect and how we use it.\n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>2.1 Collection of non-personal information</b>
        </font>
        \n
        When you create Royole accounts, download Royole software and its updates, register at Royole online retail
        stores, participate in online surveys or participate in other interactions with Royole, we will collect
        information such as occupation, language, postcode, area code and the time zone where you use Royole products.
        User Habits and Problem Finding Information --- When you join FlexPai\'s "User Experience Improvement Program",
        we will anonymously count the use of various functions of your products according to needs, so as to collect
        information about your use habits of Royole\'s official website, products and services. And when the system
        abnormally exits and crashes, we collect information about the current environment of the mobile phone which is
        easy to diagnose the problem.
        Relevant information recorded on the server side - When you use soft theme, voice assistant, browser and other
        products, Royole will collect relevant information recorded on your server side, such as upload, download,
        synchronization, browse and other user behavior-related data. These data are regarded as non-personal
        information.
        Location information - When you use Royole to provide several location-based program services and functions, we
        need to collect your location information. For example, when you do location-based search, use location-based
        advertising, use location to optimize weather functions or request map information, your location information
        may be sent back to Royole so that Royole can provide you with the correct content.
        Cookies and other technologies gather information - Royole\'s website, online services, interactive
        applications, e-mail messages and advertising campaigns may use cookies and other technologies such as pixel
        tags and website beacons to collect and store your non-personal information.
        Log information - When you visit the Royole server, our server will automatically record some log information.
        Such server log information may contain the following information: IP address, browser type, browser language,
        refer source page, operating system, date/time tag and click stream data.
        Abnormal information - collection of abnormal information when function is abnormal.\n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>2.2 Use of non-personal information</b>
        </font>
        \n
        Our collection of non-personal information, such as occupation, language, postcode, area code and time zone
        where we use Royole products, can help us better understand user behavior and improve our products, services and
        advertising.\n
        We can continuously improve the operational experience, operational performance, repair problems and improve
        functional design of products and services by analyzing the statistical data obtained by Royole\'s "User
        Experience Improvement Plan".\n
        We use cookies and other technologies to collect information that will bring you a better user experience and
        improve our overall service quality. For example, by saving your language preferences, we can display our
        services in your preferred language. We can use pixel tags to send e-mails in a readable format to users and
        tell them if they are opened. We can use this information to reduce sending e-mail to users or not to users.\n\n

        <font color="#000000">
            <b>Ⅲ. How do you selectively provide information and how do you access and update it.</b>
        </font>
        \n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>1. How do you selectively provide information</b>
        </font>
        \n
        Everyone has their own focus on privacy. Based on this, we will clearly point out the way we collect information
        so that you can choose the way to receive information.\n
        You are free to set whether to join the User Experience Improvement Plan or not. You can exit the plan by
        turning off the switch of the User Experience Improvement Plan item.\n
        You can modify the location settings of your device from the device settings, such as changing or disabling the
        location method or the location server, or modifying the accuracy of your location information to change the
        location information provided to Royole.\n
        You can modify the browser settings to reject or accept cookies according to your needs, or you can delete them
        from your storage device at any time, or notify you when writing cookies.\n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>2. Access and update of personal information</b>
        </font>
        \n
        By clicking on [https://www.royole.com/login] to log in to your account, you can access and update your personal
        information. You can also delete some personal information or ask us to delete your personal account unless we
        have to keep it for legal reasons.\n
        Whenever you use our services, we strive to enable you to access your personal information. If this information
        is incorrect, we will try to let you update or delete it quickly in various ways (unless we have to keep it for
        legitimate business or legal reasons). In updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your
        identity before processing your request.\n
        We may refuse requests that are unreasonable, requiring too much technical input, risking the privacy of others,
        or very impractical.\n
        As long as we can let you access and modify the information, and it does not require too much investment, we
        will provide it free of charge. We strive to improve the maintenance of services to protect information from
        accidental or malicious damage. Therefore, when you delete information from our service, we may not immediately
        delete the residual copies of the information from the server in use, or we may not delete the corresponding
        information from the backup system.\n\n

        <font color="#000000">
            <b>Ⅳ. Information Sharing and Information Security</b>
        </font>
        \n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>1. Sharing information with third parties</b>
        </font>
        \n
        Unless limited sharing is specified in this privacy policy, we will keep your personal information strictly
        confidential and will not share your personal information with third parties.\n
        You are authorized to share your personal information with third parties without your consent in the following
        circumstances:\n
        We share these personal information with third parties because of legal investigation, litigation, enforcement
        or other mandatory legal provisions or requirements.\n
        We provide personal information to our subsidiaries, affiliates or other trusted enterprises or individuals so
        that they can process personal information on our behalf. We require the above parties to agree to handle these
        personal information in accordance with our provisions, this Privacy Policy and any other applicable
        confidentiality and security measures.\n
        If we reorganize, merge or sell, we will continue to keep our personal information confidential and inform all
        affected users in accordance with existing privacy policy constraints before transferring all personal
        information we collect.\n
        We may reasonably share aggregated non-personal information with the public and partners based on the need to
        operate or protect users, such as in order to demonstrate the overall use trend of our products or services.\n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>2. Information Security</b>
        </font>
        \n
        We strive to protect users of Royole from unauthorized access to, tampering with, disclosure or destruction of
        the information we keep. To this end, we have taken the following measures in particular:\n
        We use SSL to encrypt many services. We will review information collection, storage and processing practices
        (including physical security measures) to avoid unauthorized access to various systems.\n
        We only allow those employees who need to know about personal information in order to help us deal with personal
        information and authorize those who deal with service companies to access personal information, and they need to
        fulfil strict contractual confidentiality obligations. If they fail to fulfil these obligations, they may be
        prosecuted for legal responsibility or terminated their relationship with Royole.\n
        For us, the security of your information is very important. Therefore, we will continue to strive to protect
        your personal information security, and implement security measures such as storage and transmission of the
        whole process of encryption, so as to prevent your information from being accessed, used or disclosed without
        authorization. At the same time, the specific content of some encrypted data, except for the user himself, other
        people have no right to access.\n\n

        <font color="#000000">
            <b>Ⅴ. Collection and use of children\'s personal information</b>
        </font>
        \n
        We recommend that children under the age of 18 use Royole products or services with the permission and guidance
        of their legal guardians.\n
        Royole will not collect his personal information without knowing that the other party is a child, nor will he
        disclose his personal information to any third party. The guardian has the right to refuse Royole and its
        affiliated companies to further collect the personal information of the guardian, or to request Royole and its
        affiliated companies to delete the personal information of the guardian. If we find that we have collected
        personal information about children under the age of 18, we will take measures to delete such information as
        soon as possible.\n\n

        <font color="#000000">
            <b>Ⅵ. Scope of Use and Revision of this Privacy Policy</b>
        </font>
        \n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>1. Scope of application of this Privacy Policy</b>
        </font>
        \n
        Our privacy policy does not apply to third-party products and/or services. Royole\'s products and services may
        contain links to third-party websites, products and services. When you use third-party products or receive
        third-party services, they may get your information. Therefore, we remind you to read the third-party privacy
        policy.\n
        At the same time, this privacy policy does not apply to collecting data from external websites after you click
        on links.\n
        <font color="#000000">
            <b>2. Revision of this Privacy Policy</b>
        </font>
        \n
        This Privacy Policy allows for adjustments. Without your express consent, we will not impair your rights under
        this Privacy Policy unless you are notified or announce your website through the e-mail address you provide.
    </string>


    <string-array name="weather_code">
        <item>Sunny</item>
        <item>Cloudy</item>
        <item>Overcast</item>
        <item>Shower</item>
        <item>Thundershower</item>

        <item>Thundershower with hail</item>
        <item>Sleet</item>
        <item>Light rain</item>
        <item>Moderate rain</item>
        <item>Heavy rain</item>

        <item>Storm</item>
        <item>Heavy storm</item>
        <item>Severe storm</item>
        <item>Snow flurry</item>
        <item>Light snow</item>

        <item>Moderate snow</item>
        <item>Heavy snow</item>
        <item>Snowstorm</item>
        <item>Foggy</item>
        <item>Ice rain</item>

        <item>Dust storm</item>
        <item>Light to moderate rain</item>
        <item>Moderate to heavy rain</item>
        <item>Heavy rain to storm</item>
        <item>Storm to heavy storm</item>

        <item>Heavy to severe storm</item>
        <item>Light to moderate snow</item>
        <item>Moderate to heavy snow</item>
        <item>Heavy snow to snowstorm</item>
        <item>Dust</item>

        <item>Sand</item>
        <item>Sandstorm</item>
        <item>Dense foggy</item>
        <item>Snow</item>
        <item>Moderate foggy</item>

        <item>Haze</item>
        <item>Moderate haze</item>
        <item>Heavy haze</item>
        <item>Severe haze</item>
        <item>Heavy foggy</item>

        <item>Severe foggy</item>
        <item>Unknown</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="wind_direction">
        <item>No Wind</item>
        <item>Northeast Wind</item>
        <item>East Wind</item>
        <item>Southeast Wind</item>
        <item>South Wind</item>

        <item>Southwest Wind</item>
        <item>West Wind</item>
        <item>Northwest Wind</item>
        <item>North Wind</item>
        <item>Whirl Wind</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="wind_force">
        <item>Breeze</item>
        <item>3-4 Level</item>
        <item>4-5 Level</item>
        <item>5-6 Level</item>
        <item>6-7 Level</item>

        <item>7-8 Level</item>
        <item>8-9 Level</item>
        <item>9-10 Level</item>
        <item>10-11 Level</item>
        <item>11-12 Level</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="wind_speed">
        <item>&lt;10m/h</item>
        <item>10~17m/h</item>
        <item>17~25m/h</item>
        <item>25~34m/h</item>
        <item>34~43m/h</item>

        <item>43~54m/h</item>
        <item>54~65m/h</item>
        <item>65~77m/h</item>
        <item>77~89m/h</item>
        <item>89~102m/h</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="air_quality">
        <item>Excellent</item>
        <item>Good</item>
        <item>Moderate</item>
        <item>Moderate</item>
        <item>Unhealthy</item>
        <item>Hazardous</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gj_warning_type">
        <item>Typhoon</item>
        <item>Storm</item>
        <item>Snowstorm</item>
        <item>Cold wave</item>
        <item>Gale</item>

        <item>Sandstorm</item>
        <item>High temperature</item>
        <item>Drought</item>
        <item>Thunder</item>
        <item>Hail</item>

        <item>Frost</item>
        <item>Dense foggy</item>
        <item>Haze</item>
        <item>Road icing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gj_warning_level">
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Yellow</item>
        <item>Orange</item>
        <item>Red</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gd_warning_type">
        <item>Storm</item>
        <item>High temperature</item>
        <item>Hail</item>
        <item>Dense foggy</item>
        <item>Road icing</item>

        <item>Haze</item>
        <item>Cold</item>
        <item>Thunderstorm</item>
        <item>Forest fire</item>
        <item>Typhoon</item>

        <item>Thunder</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gd_warning_level">
        <item>White</item>
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Yellow</item>
        <item>Orange</item>
        <item>Red</item>

        <item>Black</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="auto_update_time">
        <item>off</item>
        <item>1h</item>
        <item>3h</item>
        <item>6h</item>
        <item>12h</item>
        <item>24h</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="appwidget_text">EXAMPLE</string>
    <string name="add_widget">Add widget</string>
    <string name="database_full_exception">
        Your mobile phone space is insufficient, affecting the normal use, please clean up the file to release more
        space!
    </string>
    <string name="database_exception">database exception!</string>
</resources>
